Guide to the Harold Dwight Lasswell Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1923-1981; Series II; 25 linear feet (57 boxes)
  - Card files, extracts, notes
    - Notes (Box 163, Folder 245-247)
- Topical Files, [ca. 1930s-1970s]; Series III; 13 linear feet (29 boxes)
  Topical Files contains memoranda, notes, research data, charts, printed material, and clippings arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - ACESS Project (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Architecture (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Arts (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographies (Box 164, Folder 4-6)
  - Black character (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Character (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Chile trip, 1966 (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - China (Box 164, Folder 10-11)
  - China (Box 165, Folder 12-15)
  - Chinese thought conference, 1960 (Box 165, Folder 16-19)
  - Civil liberties (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - Communications (Box 166, Folder 21-22)
  - Community (Box 166, Folder 23)
  - Computers (Box 166, Folder 24-26)
  - Content analysis - general, Circa 1944-1949 (Box 166, Folder 27)
    See also: War Communication. Library of Congress project files - World attention survey, circa 1944-1949. See also: box 189, folder 234-237
    - British press (Box 166, Folder 28-29)
    - French press (Box 167, Folder 31-36, Box 166, Folder 30)
    - United States press (Box 167, Folder 37-38)
  - Cosmic process (Box 168, Folder 39)
  - Course material (Box 168, Folder 40)
  - Crime (Box 168, Folder 41-43)
  - Crisis (Box 168, Folder 44)
  - Developmental constructs (Box 168, Folder 45)
  - Economic development (Box 168, Folder 46)
  - Education (Box 168, Folder 47-49)
  - Elite bibliography (Box 168, Folder 50-51)
  - Elite bibliography (Box 169, Folder 52-53)
  - Environment (Box 169, Folder 54)
  - Far Eastern study year, 1962 (Box 169, Folder 55-59)
  - Futures (Box 169, Folder 60)
  - Futures (Box 170, Folder 61)
  - Games (Box 170, Folder 62)
  - Identity (Box 170, Folder 63)
  - India (Box 170, Folder 64-66)
  - Indian elites: Satish Arora's research data (Box 170, Folder 67-69)
  - Indian elites: Satish Arora's research data (Box 171, Folder 70-76)
  - Indian elites: Satish Arora's research data (Box 172, Folder 77-86)
  - Intelligence (Box 173, Folder 87)
  - International agreement project (Box 173, Folder 88)
  - Ireland (Box 173, Folder 89)
  - Japan (Box 173, Folder 90)
  - Japan trip: Tokyo seminars 1955 (Box 173, Folder 91)
  - Judicial process (Box 173, Folder 92)
  - Law: conceptions of jurisprudence (Box 173, Folder 93)
  - Lawyer (Box 173, Folder 94)
  - Method (Box 173, Folder 95)
  - Multiple sclerosis (Box 173, Folder 96)
  - New Haven (Box 173, Folder 97)
  - New York (Box 173, Folder 98)
  - Organized crime (Box 173, Folder 99)
  - Peace (Box 173, Folder 100)
  - Personality (Box 174, Folder 101)
  - Policy functions (Box 174, Folder 102)
  - Policy sciences (Box 174, Folder 103)
  - Political personality (Box 174, Folder 104)
  - Political science (Box 174, Folder 105)
  - Population and family planning (Box 174, Folder 106)
  - Privacy (Box 174, Folder 107)
  - Revolution (Box 174, Folder 108)
  - Self-observation (Box 174, Folder 109)
  - Systematic theory (Box 174, Folder 110)
  - U.S.S.R. (Box 175, Folder 111)
  - U.S. Supreme Court (Box 175, Folder 112)
  - Universities, International (Box 175, Folder 113)
  - Values
    See also: box 221, folders 85-93 See also: box 222, folders 94-99
  - Vicos project (Box 176, Folder 126-130)
  - Vicos project (Box 177, Folder 131-133)
  - War (Box 177, Folder 134)
  - War communications - Library of Congress project files
    - General
      - Argentine press (Box 177, Folder 135-136)
      - Austria (Box 177, Folder 137)
      - Brazil (Box 177, Folder 138)
      - Britain (Box 177, Folder 139-141)
      - Canada (Box 178, Folder 142)
      - Case studies (Box 178, Folder 143)
      - Categories; Categories Committee (Box 178, Folder 144)
      - Codes and coding (Box 178, Folder 145-147)
        See also: box 184, folders 177-178
      - Education (Box 178, Folder 148)
      - Elite method (Box 178, Folder 149)
      - English propaganda in the U.S. (Box 178, Folder 150)
      - Federal Communications Commission (Box 178, Folder 151)
      - Film notes (Box 178, Folder 152)
      - Forms (Box 178, Folder 153)
      - France (Box 178, Folder 154-155)
      - Germany (Box 179, Folder 156-159)
      - Ireland (Box 179, Folder 160)
      - Italy (Box 179, Folder 161-162)
      - Japan (Box 179, Folder 163)
      - Middle class movements (Box 179, Folder 164)
      - Newspapers (Box 179, Folder 165)
      - Newsreel research (Box 179, Folder 166)
      - Organization analysis code (Box 179, Folder 167)
      - Periodicals survey (Box 180, Folder 168)
      - Propaganda agents, foreign (Box 180, Folder 169)
      - Public opinion (Box 180, Folder 170)
      - Radio (Box 180, Folder 171)
      - Soviet Union (Box 180, Folder 172-173)
      - Spain (Box 180, Folder 174)
      - Speech analysis - President Roosevelt (Box 180, Folder 175)
      - Speech analysis - President Roosevelt card file indices (Box 181–183)
      - Sweden (Box 184, Folder 176)
      - Symbols (Box 184, Folder 177-178)
        See also: box 178, folders 145-147
      - U.S. vs. Winrod et al. (Box 184, Folder 179)
      - Word space count - David Kaplan (Box 184, Folder 180)
      - Miscellaneous notes (Box 184, Folder 181)
    - Cherin files
      - Analytic procedures (Box 184, Folder 182)
      - Movies (Box 184, Folder 183)
      - Opinion surveys (Box 184, Folder 184)
      - Propaganda (Box 184, Folder 185-187)
      - Propaganda (Box 185, Folder 188)
      - Radio themes (Box 185, Folder 189)
      - Treatment of foreign-born (Box 185, Folder 190)
      - Trend Research, Inc. (Box 185, Folder 191)
    - Goldsen files
      - "Axis vs. Allies" ms. (Box 185, Folder 192)
      - Case studies (Box 185, Folder 193)
      - Coding instructions (Box 185, Folder 194)
      - Community participation project (Box 185, Folder 195)
      - Content analysis (Box 185, Folder 196)
      - German news (Box 185, Folder 197)
      - Hitler data (Box 185, Folder 198)
        See also: box 186, folders 211-212
      - May Day slogans (Box 185, Folder 199)
      - Memoranda (Box 185, Folder 200)
      - Newspapers (Box 186, Folder 201)
      - Office of Censorship (Box 186, Folder 202)
      - Office of Facts and Figures (Box 186, Folder 203)
      - Posters (Box 186, Folder 204)
      - Reading notes (Box 186, Folder 205)
      - Reliability (Box 186, Folder 206)
      - Statistics 402 (Box 186, Folder 207)
      - Symbols (Box 186, Folder 208)
      - "World Press Sample": ms (Box 186, Folder 209-210)
    - Herzog files on Hitler speeches
      - Correspondence (Box 186, Folder 211-212)
      - Hitler speeches, 1939 September-1942 (Box 187, Folder 213-222)
      - Speech analysis data (Box 188, Folder 223-231)
      - Re publication (Box 189, Folder 232-233)
    - World Attention Survey - charts (Box 189, Folder 234-237)
    - World Attention Survey - charts (Box 190, Folder 238-246)
    - World Attentions Survey - charts (Box 191, Folder 247-253)
    - World Attention Survey - charts (Box 192)
- Writing of Others, [ca. 1940s-1970s]; Series IV; 7.5 linear feet (19 boxes)
  Writings of Others consists of articles, reprints, speeches, and papers sent to or collected by Lasswell. These writings are arranged alphabetically by name of author. At the end of the series are student papers, also arranged alphabetically by name of author. Similar material is arranged in Series I, but there are no writings of individuals listed in Series I arranged in this series.
  - A - Bi (Box 193, Folder 1-27)
  - Bl - Co (Box 194, Folder 28-59)
  - Co - Fl (Box 195, Folder 60-83)
  - Fo - He (Box 196, Folder 84-115)
  - Hi - Le (Box 197, Folder 116-144)
  - Li - Po (Box 198, Folder 145-176)
  - Pr - Sh (Box 199, Folder 177-198)
  - Si - Wa (Box 200, Folder 199-227)
  - Wa - Yo (Box 201, Folder 228-241)
  - Yo - Z, Unidentified (Box 202, Folder 242-249)
  - Student Papers
    - Ad - An (Box 202, Folder 250-253)
    - As - Ch (Box 203, Folder 254-265)
    - Co - Go (Box 204, Folder 266-282)
    - Gr - Ka (Box 205, Folder 283-303)
    - Ke - Ma (Box 206, Folder 304-326)
    - Ma - Po (Box 207, Folder 327-343)
    - Po - Sc (Box 208, Folder 344-353)
    - Sc - Sp (Box 209, Folder 354-364)
    - Sq - Wi (Box 210, Folder 365-380)
    - Wo - Zo, Unidentified (Box 211, Folder 381-387)
- Biographical Material and Personal Memorabilia, [ca. 1877]-1984; Series V; 5.5 linear feet (12 boxes)
  This series is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Goldsen files concerning Lasswell business following Laswell's stroke, 1977-1978 (Box 212, Folder 1-4)
  - Goldsen files concerning Laswell's death and matters after his death, 1978-1979 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - MacDougal files concerning memorials to Lasswell, 1978-1984 (Box 212, Folder 6-11)
  - Address and memo books, undated (Box 213, Folder 12)
  - Biographical and bibliographic sketches
    - General, [ circa 1946 ]-1981 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Affidavit for Army-Navy-Air Force Personnel Security Board, 1951 (Box 213, Folder 14-16)
    - Obituaries and memorial tributes, 1978-1984 (Box 213, Folder 17-19)
  - Certificates and diplomas, 1915-1976 (Box 214, Folder 20-25)
  - Family papers
    - Lasswell, Anna Prather, 1877-1943 (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Lasswell, Linden Downey, [ca. 1924]-1964 (Box 215, Folder 27-28)
    - Other, [ca. 1919]-1969 (Box 215, Folder 29)
  - Fiftieth birthday memorabilia - Committee for the Preservation of Harold D. Lasswell, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 30)
  - Financial records, [ca. 1941]-1972 (Box 216, Folder 31)
  - Juvenilia, 1912-1918 (Box 216, Folder 32)
  - Legal and medical records, 1923-1979 (Box 216, Folder 33)
  - Writings about Lasswell
    See also: box 213, folder 13
    - Brass, Paus Richard: thesis, Harvard College, 1958 (Box 216, Folder 34)
    - Levine, David D.: student paper, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 35)
    - McDougall, Derek: dissertation, Undated (Box 216, Folder 36)
    - Preiss, Jack: Camp William James, 1978 (Box 216, Folder 37)
    - Articles, 1934, 1950-1975 (Box 217, Folder 38-41)
    - Reviews of Lasswell's books, 1927-1978 (Box 217, Folder 42-45)
    - Cliipings, 1913-1972, undated (Box 217, Folder 46-50)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950, undated (Box 218, Folder 51)
  - Photographs
    See also: box 221, folders 74-84 box 223, folder 103
    - Lasswell as a child (Box 218, Folder 52)
    - Lasswell portraits (Box 218, Folder 53)
    - Album, 1915-1917 (Box 218, Folder 54)
    - 1954-1975 (Box 218, Folder 55-56)
    - Peru, 1959 (Box 218, Folder 57)
      See also: box 221, folders 74-84 See also: box 223, folder 103
    - China, India, Hong Kong, Japan, 1955-1967 (Box 218, Folder 58)
      See also: box 223, folder 102
    - N.D. (Box 219, Folder 59)
    - Lasswell friends and acquaintances (Box 219, Folder 60)
    - Children of Lasswell's friends and acquaintances (Box 219, Folder 61)
    - Lasswell's parents (Box 219, Folder 62-63)
    - Lasswell, Prather and other relatives (Box 219, Folder 64)
    - Friends of Lasswell's parents (Box 220, Folder 65)
    - Anna Prather Lasswell's album (Box 220, Folder 66)
    - Unidentified family or friends of Lasswell's parents (Box 220, Folder 67)
    - Places
      - Illinois (Box 220, Folder 68)
      - Indiana (Box 220, Folder 69)
      - Unidentified (Box 220, Folder 70)
    - Unidentified (Box 220, Folder 71-73)
    - Slides
      - Peru: Vicos, 1949-1955 (Box 221, Folder 74-75)
        See also: box 218, folder 57
      - [Peru] (Box 221, Folder 76-84)
      - Value Charts
        - Wealth-rectitude in the U.S. (1A-1G) (Box 221, Folder 85-93)
        - Rectitude-respect in the U.S. (1G-1H) (Box 222, Folder 94-95)
        - Value in the WORLD system (2A-H) (Box 222, Folder 96-98)
        - Theoretical (3) (Box 222, Folder 99)
      - Government architecture (taken by H. Peter Stern, 1966)
        See also: box 90, folder 1105
        - Israel (Box 222, Folder 100)
        - India (Box 222, Folder 101)
    - Oversize
      - Scrapbook: Japan, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 102)
      - Scrapbook: Huapra, Peru, 1960 Aug 9 (Box 223, Folder 103)
- Additional material, 1952-1978; Accession 1988-M-049
  Includes Accessions 1989-M-024, 1991-M-025, and 1991-M-075. Addition inventory by Diane E. Kaplan and Murat Dogruer, June 1991, revised April 1994.
  This addition is composed of correspondence, printed matter, biographical material, and personal memorabilia received for the Lasswell Papers since 1988. Previous smaller additions were integrated into the existing arrangement of papers. Since it was not possible to integrate the entire fourteen feet of material from Lasswell's office at the Policy Sciences Center (received from Jeremiah McKenna in 1988), as well as smaller additions from James Robinson and from Andrew Willard, this material was processed as an addition to the papers in 1991.
  Though the earliest material in the addition dates from 1954, the bulk of the papers date from 1971-1978. The material has been arranged in sections parallel to the arrangement of series in the August 1985 register. The addition includes General Files, Topical Files, and Biographical Material and Personal Memorabilia. No Writings of Others are included in this addition.
  The additional material received from the Policy Sciences Center also included printed copies, as well as drafts of Lasswell's writings. During processing these writings were rearranged into boxes 107 - 163 of the original Writings series, Series II. Duplicate copies were removed and previously unknown or unidentified writings processed. The listing in this register for Series II now reflects the addition of these materials.
  During processing, material that was similar in nature to that already found in the papers was added to Series V, Biographical Material and Personal Memorabilia. Additional types of biographical material and personal memorabilia such as video tapes and pocket diaries, as well as numerous additional photographs were arranged at the end of the addition.
  - General Files
    - Ab-Ac, 1968, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Al, 1972, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Am-An, 1971-1978, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ar, 1962, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - As, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - At-Az, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Abrahamsen, Christian, 1954, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Academic Press, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Academy for Contemporary Problems, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Access, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
      See also: box 16, folders 327-329
    - Addison-Wesley Publishing Co., 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Agger, Robert E., 1977-1978, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Agnelli Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
    - Agnelli Foundation, 1974-1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 17-25)
    - Albrecht, Arthur, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Alexander, Herbert E., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Alger, Chadwick F. and Ellie, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Alker, Haywood R., 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Allen, Jane, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Allen, Layman E., 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Alschuler, Rose, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Amara, Roy, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1975-1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - American Political Science Association, 1974-1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
      See also: box 67, folder 885-886
    - American Political Science Review, 1975, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - American Society for Political and Legal Philosophy, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - American Society of International Law, 1971-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 41-48)
    - Andriole, Stephen J., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Another Mother for Peace, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Antioch School of Law, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Anton, Tom, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Arens, Richard, 1973-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Armstrong, Fred, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Arora, Satish, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Ascher, Charles S., 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Ascher, William, 1974-1977, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Atkin, Samuel, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Atterbury, Boudinot P., 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Ba, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Be, 1968, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Bi-Bl, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Bo, 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Br, 1964, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Bu, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Barber, James D., 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Barger, Walter Kenneth, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Beach, Walter E., 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Beck, Norman W., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Benton, Charles, 1973, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Bolte, Charles G., 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Borchardt, Edward, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Boyko, Hugo and Elizabeth, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Braibanti, Ralph, 1972, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Bray, Charles W., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Brayer, Herbert O., 1973-1975, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Brewer, Garry D., 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 78-80)
    - Brewer, Garry D., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 81-82)
    - Brewer, Saundra, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Broh, Anthony, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Brown, Steven R., 1973-1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 85-89)
    - Brunner, Ronald D., 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 90-92)
    - Brunner, Ronald D., 1975-1977, undated (Box 6, Folder 93-96)
    - Bunker, Douglas R., 1974-1976, undated (Box 6, Folder 97-98)
    - Bureau of Social Science Research, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Burgess, Philip M., 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Burns, James MacGregor, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Ca, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Ce, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Ch-Ci, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Cl, 1972-1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Coa-Com, 1968, 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Con-Cou, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Cr-Cu, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Caldwell, Mary Ellen, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Caputo, David, 1971, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Cassidy, Richard J., 1973-1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Catlin, George E. G., 1972-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Center for Korean Studies, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Chen, Kan, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Clarke, James W., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Cohen, Julius, 1976-1977, undated (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Collier, David, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Columbia University, 1971-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Committee for the Future, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Congress of World Unity, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Connors, Canice D., 1972-1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 122-123)
    - Coplin, William D., 1973, 1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Corris, Richard C., 1973-1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Council on Social Graphics, 1975-1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Cowan, Louis G., 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Cunningham, Luvern, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 128)
      See also: box 28, folders 352-354
    - Da, 1970-1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - De-Di, 1972-1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Do-Du, 1969-1977 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Dai, Poeliu, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Davidson, Flora S., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Davidson, Frank, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - de Grazia, Alfred, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - de Grazia, Sebastian, 1970, 1973-1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - deLeon, Peter, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Dexter, Lewis A., 1974-1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Disney, Richard L., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Dixon, John, 1973-1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Dobyns, Henry, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Dolan, Barbara, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Dovring, Karin, 1975-1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Dronberger, Ilse, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Dror, Yehezkel, 1971-1977, undated (Box 8, Folder 145-146)
    - Dunphy, Hubert E., 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Ea-Ei, 1970-1978 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - El-Ew, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Elsevier Scientific Publishing Co., 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Ershkowitz, Miriam, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Etheredge, Lloyd S., 1973-1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 152-153)
    - Eulau, Heinz, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Evans, Luther H., 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Ewald, William R
      See: box 1, folders 10-11
    - Fa-Fe, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    - Fi-Fl, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 157)
    - Fo, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 158)
    - Fr, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Feingold, Jessica, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Finkelstein, Louis, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 161)
    - Fitch, John Samuel, 1976-1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
    - Fleischman, Joel, 1973, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Ford Foundation, 1971-1977 (Box 9, Folder 164)
    - Fox, Merritt B., 1967, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    - Fox, William T. R., 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 166)
    - Freedman, Daniel, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 167)
    - Freedman, Lawrence Zelic, 1973-1977, undated (Box 9, Folder 168-169)
    - Friedman, Otto, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 170)
    - Ga, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 171)
    - Ge, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 172)
    - Gi-Gl, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 173)
    - Go, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    - Gr, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - Gu, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - Gardner, Richard N., 1973-1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - Gast, Jan Willem D., 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - George, Alexander L., 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - Gerbner, George, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Giddens, Jackson, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Glyphs, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Godoy, Horacio, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - Goldsen, Joseph M., 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - Gordon, Edward, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Gosnell, Harold, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - Gottlieb, Stephen E., 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Green, Ralph, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Greenfield, Edward L., 1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Greenstein, Fred I., 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - Guyot, James F., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 192)
    - Ha, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 193)
    - He, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 194)
    - Hi, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 195)
    - Ho, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 196)
    - Hu-Hy, 1968, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 197)
    - Habicht, Max, 1973, undated (Box 10, Folder 198)
    - Haggerty, William J., 1973-1977, undated (Box 10, Folder 199)
    - Halachimi, Arie, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - Halfond, Jay, 1974-1977, undated (Box 11, Folder 201)
    - Hamilton, Richard, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - Hargrove, John L.
      See: box 3, folders 41-48
    - Harvard University, 1973-1977, undated (Box 11, Folder 203)
    - Haskins, Caryl, 1973-1977, undated (Box 11, Folder 204)
    - Hayden, Frederick L., 1974-1975, undated (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Heden, Carl-Goeran, 1970-1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 206)
      See also: box 16, folder 313
    - Heller, John H., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 207)
    - Helmer, Olaf, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 208)